(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Fall in Grace - Usada Pekora Birthday Live 2020
[Title: Fall in Grace - Usada Pekora Birthday Live 2020]
かつて天界は、光と秩序の神々によって統治されていた。
Long ago, the Heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order.
人間界、魔界、そして天界。
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm.
全ての界は、光の聖池によって均衡を保たれていた。
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light.
神聖なる『法』は、何人たりとも聖池に立ち入ること...
A sacred "Law" forbade any from entering the lake...
...あるいはその水を汚すことを禁じていた。
...or sullying its waters.
Fall in Grace - Usada Pekora Birthday Live 2020
[Title: Fall in Grace - Usada Pekora Birthday Live 2020]
Long ago, the Heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order.
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm.
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light.
A sacred "law" forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters.
The goddess Kronii was spending her days joyfully in the heavens.
A mischievous girl, today too she was chasing after her friends,
playing pranks and teasing them. She was a bit of a scatterbrained deity.
Another beautiful day... Weather like this really makes me want to sing!
せまい せまい あなぼこで
In the narrow, narrow hole
夢を見せあう ぼくたちは
We who show each other dreams
あの世もこの世もいられない
Cannot exist in this world or the next
ああ神様 子どもの神様
Oh God, childlike God
ぼくらはあなたの遊んだ砂場の中で
We are in the sandbox where you played
すり傷だらけです
covered in scratches
タタタ...
Tap tap...
踊るよ 回るよ
We dance, we spin
僕らの踊りはおかしな踊り
our dance is strange
踊ったつもりで 笑ったつもりで
Thinking we danced, thinking we laughed
倒れたつもりで 叫んだつもり
Thinking we fell, thinking we screamed
目がふらふら 音もふにゃふにゃ
Eyes are dizzy, sounds are muffled
足もふらふら マボロシふにゃふにゃ
Feet are unsteady, illusions are blurry
太陽も月も 空も神さまも
Sun, moon, sky, God
生み出して あなぐらぐらしは
Creating, living in a hole dwelling
抜け出せない
Can't escape
can't escape
抜け出せないから
Can't escape, so
抜け出さない
we don't escape
抜け出さないから
Don't escape, so
お目目閉じて
close your eyes
2 1 0
Two, one, zero
落ちて落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Falling, falling, let's fall
あなぐらぐらしの渦の中
Into the swirling vortex of the hole dwelling
落ちて落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Falling, falling, let's fall
いっしょに仲良くどこまでも
Together, happily, anywhere
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, the same?
きみと僕とはいつまでも
You and I forever
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, it's wrong, it's lonely, it's lonely
落ちて落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Fall, fall, let's go falling
ラララ...
La la la...
落ちて落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Fall, fall, let's go falling
ラララ...
La la la...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Same, same, isn't it the same?
ラララ...
La la la...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Same, same, isn't it the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
Forbidden, forbidden, lonely, lonely
なかま なかま あなたはいかが
Companion, companion, how about you?
なかま なかま ぼくらはなかま
Companion, companion, we are companions
あなたはなかま？ 合言葉？
Are you a companion? Password?
あなぐらせかいの合言葉？
The password for this 'hole-dwelling' world?
抜け出せない
Can't get out
抜け出せないから 教えない
Because I can't get out, I won't tell you
あなたはなかま？ さみしいなかま？
Are you a companion? A lonely companion?
奈落に生きるなかまですか
Are you a companion living in hell?
夢をかけらを飲んでいる
Drinking pieces of dreams
きみの夢もまぜまぜしていて
Mixing in your dreams too
あの世もこの世もいられない
We can't stay in the afterlife, nor in this life
目がふらふら
Eyes are dizzy
音もふにゃふにゃ
Sound is mushy
腕もふらふら
Arms are dizzy
マボロシふにゃふにゃ
Phantom is mushy
太陽も月も空も神さまも
Sun and moon, sky and God
ギトギトに鮮やかで
Viscidly vivid
抜け出せない
Can't get out
抜け出せないから 抜け出さない
Because I can't get out, I won't get out
抜け出さないから お目目閉じて
Because I won't get out, close your eyes
閉じて...
Close...
ルルル...
Lu lu lu...
落ちて落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Fall, fall, fall, let's go falling
あなぐらぐらしの渦の中
In the whirlpool of this 'hole-dwelling'
落ちて落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Fall, fall, fall, let's go falling
いっしょに仲良くどこまでも
Together, happily, everywhere
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Same, same, isn't it the same?
きみと僕とはいつまでも
With you and me, forever
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Same, same, isn't it the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
Forbidden, forbidden, lonely, lonely
落ちて落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ ラララ...
Fall, fall, let's go falling, la la la...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか ラララ...
Same, same, isn't it the same? La la la...
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
Forbidden, forbidden, lonely, lonely
虎狼来 (Kororon)
Lyrics, Music: Eve
[Song: Kororon]
[Lyrics, Music: Eve]
サンタマリア 起死回生の一打を放ってくれ
Santa Maria, fire a strike to bring me back to life
湿っぽいのはいらんな 爽快に派手にやって終い
I don't need any dampness, just do it refreshingly and flashily
その答えは自問自答の向こう側にあんだしょうがない
That answer is on the other side of self-questioning, it can't be helped
アンダーグラウンドな世界の中
Inside an underground world
井の中の蛙大会優勝者 未練たらたら
Winner of the frog-in-the-well contest, still lingering
SNSに夢中 自尊心なんてとうに無いなって
Obsessed with SNS, self-esteem is long gone
愛を謳っては 愛されたことない未体験 応えよ
Singing of love, an unexperienced feeling of never being loved, answer me
毎度退場生涯引退生活安泰で居たい
Leaving every time, I want to live a peaceful life after retiring for good
別に不満などないけれど
Well, I’m not really dissatisfied,
描いた夢と違うけれど
but bored by the view I’ve never dream
なぜか心に穴が空いたようだ
Somehow, I have sensed the anomaly, that my heart feels like having a hole in it
気づいてしまうから
since I have realized it
ありきたりな人生に
And now I put a period
今ピリオドを打て。
to my ordinary life.
爆ぜるようなこの気持ちが
The emotion that is about to pop out,
抑えようもない衝動が
and the impulse that can’t be restrained
望み通り叶わない
Fail to come true as expected;
現実になってまだまだ
still a long way to become reality
くたばってなんかないぜ
I won’t die
神に誓って泣いた思い出
as my swear to the God calls back
実態ない将来に不安定で痛い
Anxiety for that unstable future hurts
騒ぐ心の音を聞こう
Listen to my heartbeat that makes noise gravely
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
It will never die out in the dream
足を止めていられぬよう
and will never stop my pace
虎狼来 迷子ステイホーム
“Kororon,” the child who gets lost should stay home
言葉では なんとでも言えるここが正念場
I can say anything by word, and now is the critical moment
そういや外野は 愛のない Dis カッション 派手にやってくれ
The outsiders are simply making loveless discussion in a fancy way
その結果が全てなんだ 許しがたいが
Such a consequence is all the thing I can have, yet unforgivable
チャンスは1回だ まだ生かしてくれよ世界の中
Then with the only chance, let me live in this world
定かではないがまだ僕の中には
Although it is uncertain, there are so many things
数 数多 余すこともない事実が
in my mind that hard to tell
虎狼に飼いならされるこの毎日が
I hate the routine that seems like being fed to tigers and wolfs
嫌 食べられて終い
Meaning to pet them, but ending up with being eaten
実は不安しかないけれど
To be honest, I can only feel upset inside,
描いた夢もないけれど
being bored by the view I’ve never dream
だから心に穴が空いたようだ
Therefore, I have sensed the anomaly, that my heart feels like having a hole in it
気づいてしまった
And I noticed it...
ありきたりな人生に 今ピリオドを打て。
And now I put a period to such an ordinary life.
爆ぜるようなこの気持ちが
The emotion that is about to pop out,
抑えようもない衝動が
and the impulse that can’t be restrained
望み通り叶わない
Fail to come true as expected;
現実になってまだまだ
still a long way to become reality
くたばってなんかないぜ
I won’t die
神に誓って泣いた思い出
as my swear to the God calls back
実態ない将来に不安定で痛い
Anxiety for that unstable future hurts
騒ぐ心の音を聞こう
Listen to my heartbeat that makes noise gravely
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
It will never die out in the dream
足を止めていられぬよう
and will never stop my pace
虎狼来 迷子ステイホーム
“Kororon,” the child who gets lost should stay home
Woooo! Yay! / Yay!
Ha, thank you so much for coming everyone to my 3D live.
My name is Ouro Kronii from Hololive English and we have Sora-senpai!
Yay!
Hello! I'm Tokino Sora. Kon-Sora!
Yay! Kronii, Happy Birthday!
Thank you!
Very gorgeous outfit!
Thank you! Arigato gozaimasu!
Thank you! / Yay!
Oh man, look at the stage here.
Very beautiful!
Yeah! So pretty! Look at the night sky!
Wow! Kirei! Wow!
Wow! Beautiful! Wow!
Kronii, Kronii! Why did you invite me to your birthday live?
Oh, uh, well... last year, um, we hung out together a bit...
...and I had a lot of fun.
So I wanted to, um, invite you and, um, get to sing together.
I thought that would have been really great. So thank you for coming.
Ah, thank you! Yay!
Sora love you!
Oh! Oh my god! Love is such a strong word.
Um, I... I love you too.
I want to go to, uh, udon eating with you!
Oh, udon!
Yeah!
Yeah! Let's go eat! Oh my god!
Whoa, we'll like... we'll get anything! What kind of udon?
I like anything!
Anything!
Anything? Yeah, I like anything.
あとはー、ほかにはー？
What else is there?
あー、冷やしうどんとか、普通の汁ありうどんとか、温泉卵とか...
Like cold udon, regular soup udon, or with a soft-boiled egg...
おー、色々あるね！
Oh, so many kinds!
Yes! そう、色々、何でも大好き！
Yes! I love them all!
何でも、何でも大好き。
I love anything and everything.
Yes! 何でも、何でも！
Yes! Anything, anything!
あ、じゃあ一緒にディナーに行こう！
Oh, then let's go to dinner together!
Oh, dinner! Yeah! Oh my god, that would be really good!
そう、クロニー、今日のハッシュタグは？
So Kronii, what's today's hashtag?
Oh yeah! I mean, if you guys haven't already checked it out...
...right there! #krorigin
#krorigin!
And yeah, I hope you guys use this hashtag.
It's gonna be awesome, absolute cinema!
And so yeah, keep on the lookout for Fallen Grace!
Thank you so much for coming!
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
こちらこそありがとう！
Thank you as well!
これからも仲良くしてね！
Let's be good friends from now on!
Yeah, oh, それは嬉しいです！
Yeah, oh, I'm happy to hear that!
大好きなフレンドだから！
Because you're my favorite friend!
Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god!
じゃあ、またねー！
Well, see you later!
Congratulations!
Oh, thank you! Yay!
残響散歌
[Song: Zankyou Sanka]
誰が袖に咲く幻花
An illusional flower blooms on someone's sleeve
ただそこに藍を落とした
With a drip of deep blue
派手に色を溶かす夜に
Splashes of colors dissolve into the night
銀朱の月を添えて
With the silver-red moon on the side
転がるように風を切って
I cut through the wind like rolling
躓くごとに強くなった
And became stronger every time I stumbled
光も痛みも怒りも全部抱き締めて
Embracing everything from light to pain to anger
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If I am not chosen, just be the one to choose
声よ轟け 夜のその向こうへ
Let the voice resonate beyond the night
涙で滲んでた
That blurred in tears
あんなに遠くの景色まで
To the faraway landscape
響き渡れ
Resonate far and wide
何を奏でて？ 誰に届けたくて？
By playing what? To reach whom?
不確かなままでいい
It's okay to be unsure
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the emotions
どんなに長い葛藤も
Or how long the dilemma has lingered
歌と散れ 残響
May they all scatter in echoes
ただ一人舞う千夜
Alone dancing in one thousand nights
違えない帯を結べば
And tying the sashes that cannot be mistied
派手な色も負かす様に
To get the better of the vivid colors
深紅の香こそあはれ
The deep red scent is so profound
この先どんなつらい時も
No matter how hard it will become along the way
口先よりも胸を張って
I will take pride rather than be all mouth
抱いた夢の明かりを全部
And just trace every single light of dreams
辿るだけ
I have had
逃げ出す為 ここまで来たんじゃないだろ？
I have not come this far to run away, have I?
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If I am not chosen, just be the one to choose
声をからして
Screaming myself hoarse
燃える花のように
Like a burning flower
闇魔を照らしたら
If I shed light to the dark space
曖昧すぎる正解も
The all-too-vague right answer
譜面にして
May turn into music
夜を数えて 朝を描く様な
As if counting the nights to draw the morning
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
And ring vividly
どんなに深い後悔も
No matter how deep the regret
どんなに高い限界も
Or how high the limit
掻き消して 残響
May they all vanish in echoes
In the heavenly realm, there is a Lake of Light that controls all worlds...
...and Kronii would always observe the human world from there out of curiosity.
and Kronii would always observe the human world from there out of curiosity
As the curious Kronii continued observing,
a desire grew within her to visit not only the heavenly realm but also the human world,
where she could talk to people and play tricks on them
I want to go down to the human world
I want to play some pranks
Heehee
バグ
[Song: Bug]
Lyrics, Music: かいりきベア
[Lyrics, Music: Kairiki Bear]
迷子 迷子 真只中 さあ
Lost, lost, right in the middle of it. Come on.
パ パ パラ パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-paranoia!
ギコ ギコ My Heart(こころ)剪定
Giko, giko, my heart is pruned.
パ パ パラ パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-paranoia!
退路 退路 断った絡まった
The way back is broken, I'm tangled up in it.
パ パ パラ パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-paranoia!
SAD SAD 突っ伏してカラ
SAD SAD, get down on your knees.
ぱ ぱ ぱ La ぱーらのーい「ド」
Pa-pa-pa La-pa-pa-parano-id!
さあ バ バ バグ さあ バグバグ
Come on, bu-bu-bug, bug-bug.
タ タ タグ 才能のタグ
Ta-ta-tag, talent tag.
もう ハ ハ 剥グ 感情は剥グ
Already ha-ha-peeled off, emotions are peeled off.
発症「クルシイ」は嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌
Onset of 'Painful' is hate hate hate, hate hate hate.
まあ！ 絶叫な感情落下
Oh! Screaming emotional fall.
パッパラノーイ「ア」
Pappa-paranoia!
溺れ声上げてはぐるぐる
Drowning in a drowning sound and then going round and round.
まあ⚠︎ 絶体絶命落下
Well, in a fatal fall.
やったラ滅多ラ
Recklessly.
沈めユメユメ 嫌嫌嫌
Sink, don't dream, hate hate hate.
さあ バ バ バグさ バグバグ
Come on, bu-bu-bug, bug-bug.
的ハズレズレ慈愛嫌嫌
Missing the mark, love, hate hate.
さあ バ バ バグさ バグバグ
Come on, bu-bu-bug, bug-bug.
解答(こたえ)絶え絶え 嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌
The answer is fading away, hate hate hate, hate hate hate.
狂狂 ぱっかーん警報
Crazy, crazy, crackle alarm!
待って無理 ぐるぐる
Wait, it's impossible, round and round.
せーので回れ
Round and round we go!
(狂狂狂狂)
(Crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy!)
ｱｱｱｱｱ ぱっかーん警報
Aaaaaaa, crackle alarm!
やっぱ無理 ぐるぐる
Still impossible, round and round.
あんよに鎖
Chains on my ankles.
(狂狂狂狂)
(Crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy!)
エンドレス病み…？
Endless sickness...?
抱っこ 抱っこ いらない子だ
Cuddle, cuddle, unwanted child.
パ パ パラ パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-paranoia!
いい子 いい子 「頑張れ」の氾濫
Good boy, good boy, flood of 'go for it'.
アドミニストレイター 嗚呼
Administrator, aha!
さあ バ バ バグ さあ バグバグ
Come on, bu-bu-bug, bug-bug.
ラ ラ ラグ ランタイムラグ
La-la-lag, runtime lag.
ロ ロ ログ 反抗のログ
Lo-lo-log, log of defiance.
バ バ バグ ぱっぱぱ La ぱっぱ
Bu-bu-bug, pappa-la-pappa.
パーラノーイ「ア」
Paranoia!
ぱパーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-paranoia!
ぱパーラノーイ「ア」嫌嫌嫌
Pa-paranoia! Hate hate hate.
さあ 絶叫な感情落下
Come on, screaming emotional fall.
パ パラノーイ「ア」
Pa-paranoia!
左右行方もぐるぐる
Left and right, whereabouts is also going round and round.
悲惨⚠ 限界脳狂っちゃって
Misery! My brain's gone crazy at the limit.
やったラ滅多ラ
Recklessly.
ヤミ迷え酔え
Lost in the dark, drunk.
イナイ イナイ ばあ
Peek-a-boo!
イナイ イナイ ×点(ばってん)
Not there, not there, 'X' mark.
絶叫な感情落下
Screaming emotional fall.
パッパラノーイ「ア」
Pappa-paranoia!
溺れ声上げてはぐるぐる
Drowning in a drowning sound and then going round and round.
まあ⚠︎ 絶体絶命落下
Well, in a fatal fall.
やったラ滅多ラ
Recklessly.
凍え枯れ果て 嫌嫌嫌
Freezing, withering away, hate hate hate.
さあ バ バ バグさ バグバグ
Come on, bu-bu-bug, bug-bug.
爛れ荒れ荒れ 悲哀嫌嫌
Festering, roughened, sorrow, hate hate.
さあ バ バ バグさ バグバグ
Come on, bu-bu-bug, bug-bug.
暗闇(クロ)マミレ理性
Covered in darkness, reason...
嫌嫌嫌 今今今
Hate hate hate, now now now.
嫌嫌嫌嫌嫌嫌嫌嫌嫌
Hate hate hate hate hate hate hate hate hate.
この世で造花より綺麗な花は無いわ
There are no flowers more beautiful than artificial flowers in this world.
何故ならば総ては嘘で出来ている
Because everything is made of lies.
antipathy world
フォニイ
[Song: Phony]
Lyrics, Music: ツミキ
[Lyrics, Music: Tsumiki]
絶望の雨はあたしの傘を突いて
The rain of despair hits my umbrella,
湿らす前髪とこころの裏面
dampening my bangs and the back of my heart.
煩わしいわ
It's so annoying.
何時しか言の葉は疾うに枯れきって
Before I knew it, words had already withered away,
事の実があたしに熟れている
and the truth is ripening within me.
鏡に映り嘘を描いて
Reflected in the mirror, painting a lie,
自らを見失なった絵画
a painting that has lost its own self.
パパッパラパッパララッパッパ
Pa-pa-pa-la, pa-pa-la-la-pa-pa.
謎々かぞえて遊びましょう
Let's count riddles and play.
タタッタラタッタララッタッタ
Ta-ta-tala, ta-ta-la-la-ta-ta.
何故何故此処で踊っているでしょう
Why, oh why, are we dancing here?
簡単なことも解らないわ
I don't even understand simple things.
あたしって何だっけ
Who was I again?
それすら夜の手に絆されて
Even that is bound by the hands of night,
愛のように消える
and disappears like love.
さようならも言えぬ儘 泣いた
Crying without even being able to say goodbye,
フォニイ
Phony.
嘘に絡まっている
Entangled in lies,
あたしはフォニイ
I am a phony.
嘘吐きは　誰そ彼時に　愛なり合って
Liars fall in love at twilight
色の目が見た　音を解いている
Coloring eyes are unraveling the sound they saw
鏡に映る私を欠いて　誰もが　見ましかたベック
Lacking my reflection in the mirror, everyone's a seen-it-all beck
どうして愛なんてものに群がり　それを欲して生きるの
Why do we flock to something like love and live wanting it?
妥協も泳いでいる夜の電車が　通り過ぎていく
The night train, in which compromise also swims, passes by
踊り明かせよ
Dance until the dawn
騙して　歌いましょう
Let's deceive and sing
なぜなぜ　ここが痛むのでしょう
Why, oh why, does it hurt here?
散々な日々は通らないわ
These terrible days won't pass
刹那の雨は止まないわ
The momentary rain won't stop
さよならも言えぬまま泣いた
I cried without being able to say goodbye
フォニイ　フォニイ　フォニイ
Phony, Phony, Phony
嘘に絡まっている
Entangled in lies
簡単なこともわからないわ
I don't even understand simple things
あたしって何だっけ
What am I, again?
それすら夜の手の　絆されて
Even that is bound by the hands of the night
哀の様に
Like sorrow
さよなら　またねと呟いた
I whispered, 'Goodbye, see you later'
フォニイ　フォニイ　フォニイ
Phony, Phony, Phony
嘘に絡まっている私は
I, entangled in lies, am...
フォニイ
A phony
造花だけが知ってる　秘密のフォニイ
A secret phony that only artificial flowers know
Way 2 U
[Song: Way 2 U]
Lately I realized
I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know, do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree
I can feel the rain wash over
Us...
Yeah...
Can you hear my heart like thunder
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through
The cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side
And my heart is beating in double time
In every moment you make me feel alive
I can feel the rain wash over
Us...
Yeah...
Can you hear like thunder
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through
The cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Way to you
The goddess Kronii's desire to go to the human world and cause mischief grew.
And so, she broke the rules and set foot in the Lake of Light.
The disturbance in the lake drew the attention of the Heavenly Guardians...
...who seized Kronii and imprisoned her in a cage.
Wait, I haven't done anything yet!
I was just interested in humans and just wanted to talk!
ヴィラン
[Song: Villain]
きっと手を繋ぐだけでゾッとされる
I'm sure just holding hands would give them the creeps
馬鹿げた競争（レース）抜けたら通報される
If I leave this foolish race, I'll be reported
突然変異じゃない　ただの僕さ
It's not a mutation, it's just me
XとかYとか
X or Y...
べき論者様は善悪多頭飼い
Mr. 'Should-be' keeps a menagerie of good and evil
僕が君を“侵害”するって言いふらしてる
He's spreading rumors that I'm 'violating' you
Oh...
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals
違う服着て君の前では
Wearing different clothes,
男子のフリする
I'll pretend to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand,
迎えにきて下さい
please come and get me
顔も知らない誰かにとって
To someone whose face I don't even know,
僕はもうヴィラン
I'm already a villain
Oh... 蛇蝎ライフ
Oh... A detested life
挙句の
In the end,
糜爛
it festers
逸脱の性をまたひた隠す
Hiding my deviant nature once again
雄蕊と雄蕊じゃ立ち行かないの?
Can't two stamens make it work?
ねぇ知ってんのか乱歩という作家のことを
Hey, do you know the author named Rampo?
Import you
造花も果ては実を結ぶ
Even artificial flowers eventually bear fruit
ぶるってんじゃねーよ 多種多様の性
Don't be trembling, the many varieties of sexuality
愛かなしい哀かなしい話をしようっか
Shall we talk about a love-sad, sorrow-sad story?
ゼラチン質の「で？」
A gelatinous "so?"
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
可能性に幸あれ
Blessings to the possibilities,
僕のハート1LDK
my heart is a 1LDK
嫉妬くらいはさせてよ
At least let me be jealous
Hi there モットーYOLO
Hi there, the motto is YOLO
微熱愛でいいのに
A slight-fever love would have been enough
誰も知らない 知られたくない皮膚の下
Underneath the skin that no one knows...
素晴らしき悪党共に捧げる唄
A song dedicated to all the wonderful scoundrels
骨まで演じ切ってやれ悪辣に
Play the part to the bone, with malice
残酷な町ほど綺麗な虹が立つ
The more cruel the town, the more beautiful the rainbow
猥雑広告に踊るポップ体の愛
Love in pop-fonts dancing in crude advertisements
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals
違う服着て君の前では
Wearing different clothes,
男子のフリを!
I'll pretend to be a boy!
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand,
ここだよ
I'm right here
顔も知らない誰かにとって
To someone whose face I don't even know,
僕はもうヴィラン
I'm already a villain
蛇蝎ライフ
A detested life,
挙句の果ての糜爛
a festering end
Man... I don't know why I'm here.
I don't even deserve to be here.
I'm a goddess.
I should be treated like one.
Ugh, this sucks.
Go away.
La di da di da di da di da...
Oh what nice weather today!
Actually no I don't know if it's nice weather.
Uh... Hello? Hello?
Oh, hello!
Hi!
What are you doing here, you beautiful blue woman?
In a cage?
This is a gazebo? It kind of looks like a gazebo at first.
This is a gazebo? It looks like one at first.
Yeah, it's a gazebo.
Well-deserving for a goddess like me, if you can't tell.
Well-deserving for a goddess, if you can't tell.
Oh yeah.
Oh, you're a goddess?
Yeah. I mean, my beauty is pretty telling, so...
Oh... well, yeah, you know... you're decent.
Decent!?
Yeah. Yeah, I can see...
I can see the... yeah, I can see goddess vibes.
What?
Okay, that's a little disrespectful.
I've never heard this before.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, look who you're talking to.
Oh, okay.
Who... who are you?
Who do you think you are?
To be talking... You don't even deserve to know my name. No.
You don't even deserve to know my name. No.
What!?
You're in a cage!
Excuse me?
You're like imprisoned!
No, you just said gazebo! It's not a cage!
No, it's a cage!
It's a gazebo!
It's a cage!
If it's a gazebo, then get out of the gazebo then!
If it's a gazebo, then get out of it then!
I can't!
Why can't you get out of the gazebo!?
Because I'm weak...
for now.
Oh, you're weak?
Yeah, I need to be protected.
No, it wasn't even that bad.
Oh, but you did do something bad.
And now you're stuck in this gazebo
with the dead fly or whatever that is.
Hey!
It may look like a fly, but it's...
it's like my moral support...
Good for you. You can't talk to it like that.
Why are you talking to a dead fly?
Well, do you think I have anyone else to talk to?
Oh, so you don't deny that it's a dead fly?
It's... I mean... what are you?
Like, what's that little thing on your head?
It's... it's... it's DIFFERENT from
the halo on the dead fly, okay!
Maybe YOU'RE a fly.
Maybe you have wings...
What's the difference between you and that thing?
Do I LOOK like a fly?
Yeah!
I'm not talking to you anymore.
You can stay in there for eternity!
I'm leaving!
Wait, hold on! Hey!
Come back here, beautiful woman!
Come back here! Yoo-hoo! Hello!
Hello, beautiful woman! Hello, hello, hello!
Hi, yeah, yeah. Um, so... um...
If you happen to open this cage...
...you know, you can put it on the tab.
Do you even have money?
Uh... it can be something else.
Something even more valuable.
More valuable than money? More valuable than money?
You're not lying to me, are you?
Yes. And something that comes with...
...the price of free is... guess.
My companionship.
Friend?
Maybe not a friend. I said my companionship.
Goodbye!
Hey! Hey! Come on! Okay, maybe for a day!
Hello? For a day! For a day!
For a day?
Yeah. Now I look like a lonely ass...
Oh, no, not loneliness! Shhh.
It's okay, it's okay if you're lonely.
You know what, actually, I'm an angel.
Uh-huh. We should get along.
I am feeling awfully kind right now.
Oh... then maybe you should...
Please beg.
If you beg, I'll let you out.
Now beg.
I'm gonna speak to your higher-ups about it.
Well, you can't speak to my higher-ups if you're in this cage.
When I get out of here, you will be fired!
How are you gonna get out without me?
Do you want to take a bet? Do you want to take a gamble?
Or do you want to just free me? You should just free me.
And then maybe I'll beg, or whatever you want.
Why would you beg?
At the price of my companionship!
I'm breaking the fourth wall! I'm here to let you out!
Hey! Just let me out here already!
Now beg.
I don't...
It's the magic word. It's just a magic
word that starts with P.
Pray?
Please! Please! Please!
Finally! Finally! Okay.
Fine, because I'm so kind.
Just one please and it would
all have been over, okay?
Okay, let's go. It's a big door, it's a big door.
Yeah, it is. You got this.
Any day now...
It's okay, I'm an angel...
I can do this for...
...my beautiful friend, my one-day friend.
Beautiful friend! I will release thee!
Woo!
Wow!
Oh my god, you did it!
Wow! Yay!
How did I fall there?
Yay! Why did I bother? You're free! Woo-hoo!
Oh yeah! Let's go! Good for you!
Give me your hand please.
I need to get down from here.
You can't even let yourself out. Okay.
Thank you very much. Yeah, that's more like it.
I really put you in your place.
Okay.
That was really... okay. You know what, I'll let it slide because you freed me.
Yeah, that's how you show appreciation.
Well, I think we should celebrate!
Wow! Celebrate your freedom! Yeah, yeah!
That would be so good. We're gonna like...
You're gonna treat me to something, right? I'll treat you to something afterwards.
Okay.
And then I'll put a good word in to your
higher-ups and it'll be wonderful.
I don't even have higher-ups. You keep saying I have higher-ups.
You never know. Life is surprising.
Really?
Yeah. I mean, I'm sure you also have a boss too.
Yay! Yay!
Ow! Ow!
Yay! When did you get so strong? Ow!
I've been training recently.
Wow! It shows! Yay!
Your hands are so big.
Oh, don't make it weird.
I didn't mean to.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Lyrics, Music: syudou
[Title: Bitter Choco Decoration]
[Lyrics, Music: syudou]
人を過度に信じないように
So as not to trust people too much
愛さないように 期待しないように
Not to love, not to expect
かと言って角が立たないように
But not to be confrontational
気取らぬように 目立たぬように
Not to be pretentious, not to stand out
誰一人傷つけぬように
So as not to hurt anyone
虐めぬように 殺さぬように
Not to bully, not to kill
かと言って偽善がバレないように
But not to be exposed as a hypocrite
威張らないように
Not to boast
軽いジョークやリップサービスも
Not to forget light jokes and lip service
忘れぬようにどんな時も
To remember them at all times
笑って愛嬌振りまくように
Always laughing and charming
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
兎角言わずにたんと召し上がれ
Enjoy it without saying anything
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
You must correct your prejudices
頭空っぽその後に
If the empty head
残る心が本物なら
leaves a real heart behind
きっと君だって同じ事
Surely you are the same
「ところで一つ伺いますが...
“By the way, may I ask one thing...
...先日何処かで？・・・やっぱいいや」
...Did you happen to be somewhere the other day? Nah, forget it”
無駄に自我を晒さぬように
So as not to expose the ego unnecessarily
話さぬように 分からぬように
Not to talk, not to understand
でも絶対口を閉ざさぬように
But definitely not to keep the mouth shut
笑わすより笑われるように
To be laughed at rather than to make others laugh
人をちゃんと敬うように
To respect people properly
崇めるように 讃えるように
To worship, to praise
でも決して嫌味にならないように
But never to become sarcastic
ふざけないように
Not to joke around
集団参加の終身刑
Lifetime imprisonment of group participation
またへーこらへーこら言っちゃって
Again, heave-ho, heave-ho
「あれっ、前髪ちょーぜつさいきょーじゃん！」
“Oh, your bangs are super cool!”
とかどーでもいーのに言っちゃって
Saying things that don't matter
毎朝毎晩もう限界
Every morning, every night, I've had enough
宗教的社会の集団リンチ
Group lynching in a religious society
でも決して発狂しないように
But never to go crazy
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す
Sometimes lonely love stains you
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
立つ鳥の後きっと糞のアート
The art of bird droppings after they fly away
初めはあんな大層な
At first, I lined up such...
大言壮語を並べたが
...grandiose words.
嫌よ嫌よも好きの内
But hate and love are two sides of the same coin
「いやはやしかし今日が初めてで
“Well, today is the first time
こんなとはね 君センスあるよ」
You have a good sense”
恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション
In the season of love, bitter chocolate decoration
恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
With feelings of love, bitter chocolate decoration
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U
F-U-C-K Y-O-U
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
皆が望む理想に憧れて
Yearning for the ideal everyone desires
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
個性や情は全部焼き払い
Incinerating all individuality and emotions
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
Killing desires and egos, burying them in the ground
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
僕は大人にやっとなったよママ
I have finally become an adult, Mom
明日もきっとこの先も
Tomorrow and surely beyond
地獄は続く何処までも
Hell continues endlessly
嗚呼 だからどうか今だけは
Ah, so please, just for now
子供の頃の気持ちのままで
Stay with the feelings of a child
一糸まとわずにやってこうぜ
Let's go without a stitch of clothing
「ああ思い出した！あんたあの時の
“Ah, I remembered! You were the one then...
生真面目そうな…やっぱいいや」
...who looked so serious. Nah, forget it”
いやはや
Iyahaya
Oh, thank goodness.
Okay, well, I'm free now,
so I can finally get going.
Woohoo! Yeah! Woohoo!
Wait!
I just got out of here.
What's going on? Why?
Don't just stand there, do something!
Why?
Oh...
What happened?
Oh, what the heck?
Where my... where my beautiful clothes?
What?
Oh my god!
My... my long luscious hair?
What happened?
I can't...
What is this? I can't even take it off.
I mean, oh god,
at least I still look beautiful, but like,
what happened?
Oh man, I don't know what's going on.
Oh, what is this place anyway?
嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
No, no, no, no
残機
Lyrics, Music: ACAね
[Title: Remaining Lives / Lyrics, Music: ACAne]
しょっぱいぜ
It's salty
初めて嗅いで舐めた出会い
The first encounter I smelled and licked
自暴自棄です
It's desperation
平均的な正論が貧乏
Average righteous arguments are poor
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome
ニンニク増しで目指した健康体
Aiming for a healthy body with extra garlic
腹歌満たしてる
Filling up with belly songs
優等生
An honor student
無知なフリして踊っちゃって
Pretending to be ignorant and dancing
欠点です
It's a flaw
現状把握しちゃうから中断中
In the middle of stopping because I grasp the situation
もう譲渡
Transferring already
見せびらかし合いましょ劣等感
Let's show off our inferiority complexes to each other
もう変えられゃしないってわかってるからぁ？
Because I know it can't be changed anymore, right?
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An intuitive, selfish, incomprehensible player
求められたなら三次会
If requested, a third after-party
くだらん口喧嘩でマシになんだ
Getting better with stupid verbal fights
モットーもっと？
Motto, more?
もう意外と辛いのに
Even though it's unexpectedly tough already
うざいくらい 叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
The days I won't give up, even if I shout
or get hit until it's annoying
栄養になってまた 汚しあえ残機
Becoming nourishment, let's soil each other
again, remaining lives
わかんなくて 上がんなくて脊髄反射の涙腺は
Not knowing, not going up, the tear glands'
spinal reflex
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice, I'm grateful
試したいわ あたたかくて絶体絶命な
I want to try, warm and desperate
夜は気持ちい平凡な生活 ゆめみたけど
The night feels good, I dreamed of an
ordinary life, but
先手必勝が 気持ちいいな
The first move for victory feels good
帰ってすぐに水やり 人間の営み
Watering the plants as soon as I get home,
human activities
実のところ恵まれても 虚無感が友だち
Actually, even if blessed, emptiness is my friend
眠気覚まし耳打ち 飲み干すまで合図血
Whispering to wake up from sleepiness,
the signal blood until it's drained
仲良しこよしの時間
Time for being close buddies
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An intuitive, selfish, incomprehensible player
求められたなら三次会
If requested, a third after-party
細かいご指摘も有り難き
Grateful for even the detailed pointers
結局 瞳孔開いてしまうのに
Even though my pupils end up dilating anyway
うざいくらい 叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
The days I won't give up, even if I shout
or get hit until it's annoying
栄養になってまた 汚しあえ？残機
Becoming nourishment, let's soil each other
again? Remaining lives
わかんなくて 上がんなくて脊髄反射の涙腺は
Not knowing, not going up, the tear glands'
spinal reflex
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice, I'm grateful
試したいわ あたたかくて絶体絶命な
I want to try, warm and desperate
夜は気持ちい平凡な生活 ゆめみたけど
The night feels good, I dreamed of an
ordinary life, but
先手必勝が 気持ちいいな
The first move for victory feels good
ただ穏やかでいたい誰にも迷惑かけたくはないと思うが
I just want to be calm, I don't want to cause
trouble for anyone, I think, but
戦わないと 撫でてもらえない
If I don't fight, I won't get patted
単純明快でした
It was simple and clear
うざいくらい 叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
The days I won't give up, even if I shout
or get hit until it's annoying
栄養になってまた 汚しあえ残機
Becoming nourishment, let's soil each other
again, remaining lives
わかんなくて 上がんなくて脊髄反射の涙腺は
Not knowing, not going up, the tear glands'
spinal reflex
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice, I'm grateful
言いたいことジャンケン ご愛顧じゃまずは
Rock-paper-scissors with what I want to say,
first of all, with your patronage
実感湧くまで 拵え
Preparing until I feel it's real
すぐ吐けなくて 呆気なくて脊髄反射の涙腺は
Unable to spit it out soon, being anti-climactic,
the tear glands' spinal reflex
萎んだ脳で歌えて感謝です
Grateful to be able to sing with a shriveled brain
だりいし痒いし薄っぺらいくだらないことで笑いたかった
It's bothersome, itchy, and thin, I wanted to
laugh at stupid things
賄いじゃ満たされない不安感
A sense of unease that can't be filled by
a staff meal
暴れるのは疲れる でも侮れない
Going wild is exhausting, but I can't underestimate it
傷にはセッションで絶頂で健康できもちいな
For wounds, it feels good to be healthy and at
the peak with a session
アイデンティティ
Lyrics, Music: Kanaria
[Title: Identity / Lyrics, Music: Kanaria]
あ、ちょっと君に伝えたい何かがあったような
Ah, it seems like there was something I wanted
to tell you
けったい真逆の踊るベールサカサマだと知って
Knowing it's an upside-down, strange,
opposite dancing veil
好意とは魅惑のプログラムただ差し詰めここから行き着くは愛
Affection is a charming program, essentially,
what we arrive at from here is love
アイデンティティそれは嗜好のアイデンティティ
Identity, that's the identity of preference
アイデンティティ唸れ 君一人のせい
Identity, howl, it's all your fault
まだ捨てないで待ってそれは一つ二つのデスティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait, that's one or
two destinies
繋げてハッピー 落ちる流れ星と歪なあの星
Connect them and be happy, with a falling
shooting star and that distorted star
ララララ～
Lalalala~
重なる面影に寄り添うそっと君に寄り添う
Snuggling up to the overlapping vestige,
softly snuggling up to you
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込むハート光るあなたのアイデンティティ
The bursting vision, a heart jumping into the chest,
your shining identity
アイデンティティ
Identity
難儀プライド
Troublesome pride,
飛び込めデンジャラス
jump into danger,
さっと羽ばたく
suddenly fluttering
強気な狂気と
with strong madness,
そんで裏切り
and then betrayal,
お涙頂戴
begging for tears.
ランブラララto
Rum-bura-rara to
足取りデンジャラス
dangerous steps,
背後隠れた
focusing on the two
二人にフォーカス
hidden behind.
やっと見つけた
Finally found
不思議の正体
the true form of the mystery.
きっと恋とは真逆のプログラム
Surely love is a program the opposite of this,
ただ差し詰めここから行き着くは
in the end, it all leads to...
アイデンティティ
Identity,
それは希望のアイデンティティ
that is a matter of hope. Identity,
アイデンティティ唸れ
Identity, roar,
君一人のせい
it's all your fault alone.
まだ捨てないで待って
Don't throw it away yet, wait,
それは一つ二つのデスティニー
that's one or two destinies.
すぐさまハッピー
Immediately happy,
落ちる流れ星と
falling with the shooting star
歪なあの星
and that distorted star.
重なる面影に寄り添う
Nestle up to the overlapping memories,
そっと君に寄り添う
gently nestle up to you.
弾けだす視界
The field of vision bursts,
胸に飛び込むハート
a heart jumps into my chest,
刻むあなたの
your identity is carved,
アイデンティティ
your identity.
And now, it's time for our
special guest to appear.
Um, Wada-mama, please come in!
誕生日おめでとうございます!
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you very much!
Um, I was hoping to have Wada-mama appear
at this year's birthday celebration.
So I tried to reach out,
and she accepted, and I'm so happy!
最初お話が来た時は、すごいびっくりしたんだけど...
I was really surprised when I first got the offer, but...
今日はすごいお誕生日の素敵な日なので...
since today is such a wonderful birthday...
ここに来れて、とっても嬉しいです。
I'm very happy to be here.
おめでとうございます!
Congratulations!
私もうれしいです!
I'm happy too!
来てくれて、ありがとうございます!
Thank you for coming!
And, um, since we have this opportunity,
can I ask Wada-mama some questions?
うん、いいよ。
Yeah, sure.
Um... like, let's say...
hmm, what's your favorite food?
あんこです。
Red bean paste.
And then?
あんこです。
Red bean paste.
Only Anko?
それだけ?
Just that?
嘘、嘘やけど!
I'm lying, I'm lying!
いっぱいあるけど、あんこが一番好きです。
I have many, but I like red bean paste the best.
Okay, I'm gonna keep that in mind for next time.
Um, in that case... oh, I have one more question.
Um, what kind of game do you like?
えっとね、RPGと...
Well, RPGs and...
えっと、ローグライクのゲームが好きです。
um, I like roguelike games.
アクションが苦手。
I'm not good at action.
ゲーマーですね!
You're a gamer!
でも簡単なのが好きです。
But I like simple ones.
Oh, that's so nice!
And, um, oh yeah!
I have some exciting news to share together with Wada-mama!
And please, take a look at this!
[Birthday 2026]
And we have so much this time too! It's going to be so awesome!
And this illustration was drawn by none other than Wada-mama!
描きました!
I drew it!
She's so talented! Oh my god, so happy!
Um, was there a theme or like a particular detail you focused on for this illustration?
ハッピ用のイラストなので、ちょっと派手めに...
It's an illustration for a happi, so I made it a bit flashy...
なんかこう、でっかくみんなが楽しんで着れるような絵にしました。
I made it like, a big illustration that everyone can enjoy wearing.
可愛く描けたと思います。
I think I drew it cutely.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いです!
It's incredibly cute!
Yay! And, um, well let's go through the details!
First, we have this! Ta-da!
[Eternal Kronie Happi]
ここでハッピ売っちゃった!
I sold the happi here!
It's the Eternal Kronie Happi...
...design on the back...
...and you can show your support.
That'd be so cool!
Woo! Yay! Whoo!
And then, uh, we have this next.
Tada!
Oh, かあいい！
Oh, how cute!
It's going to be a Kronii Love! Button Badge.
And, 缶バッジ、yay!
And, button badge, yay!
Yay! キラキラ！
Yay! Sparkly!
And it's a heart-shaped and glittery holo... whoa, whoa, whoa!
Can badges!
And it's going to be perfect for fan activities.
And you can combine it with the next product...
...which is this one! Yay!
It's an Oshi Bag! Yay!
Whoa!
And it comes with a clear window...
...where you can display merch.
Like maybe a plushie, or like the can badge.
So keep that in mind. Woohoo!
And then next, we have this!
Oh, かあいい！
Oh, how cute!
Yay!
Um, if you haven't seen already, it's based off of my...
...well not next, my outfit.
Divine Chibi Plushie Keychain!
And it's going to be so exciting! Yay! Yay!
Yay! キラキラ！
Yay! Sparkly!
Oh, かあいい！Ow!
Oh, how cute! Ow!
And then there's a full set purchase bonus!
And, yay!
And, uh, the limited quantity includes original card...
...with hand-written signature.
And then the second one is a bonus voice pack...
...called Reminiscence.
And then don't worry, even when those run out...
...you still get, um, other bonuses.
Like original card...
...with foil-stamped replica signature.
And then the voice pack!
So don't worry! And, yeah!
Once again, if you want to see the entire summary...
...here's the full set!
Yay! Yay! Whoa!
And then, if you're going to buy, the full set is the way to go, obviously.
And that's all for Ouro Kronii's birthday!
Woohoo! Yay!
And then, yeah, go be sure to buy it everyone!
And we have even more news!
Whoa! Take a look at this! Woohoo!
Um, so, the release of my first physical EP...
'Way2U' has been officially decided.
Sales will start right away after the stream ends.
And the album contains five tracks!
Yay! Yay!
And this includes 'Way2U', 'Storm'...
'I'm Human Too', 'Hibiscus'...
...and of course the classic 'Daydream'.
Yay! Yay!
And every song is really special...
...so I want everyone to listen.
And there's going to be a CD...
...plus an LP vinyl version.
So maybe you can compare them and see which one you like better.
And plus, it comes with a hand-signed poster, um...
...but there's a limited amount, so be sure to check!
Yay! Yay!
And then, 'Way2U' will be released as a digital single on 3/15...
...which is March 15th...
...and distribution starts at midnight Japan time tonight.
So don't miss it!
Yay! Yay!
And you can check the description for the sales site.
And then... whew, that was a mouthful.
But after this, I'd like to sing one song together...
...with Wada-mama. Yay!
And I wanted to sing this song ever since I asked...
...so I'm really looking forward to it. Yay!
...so I want to sing this song, I'm looking forward to it. Yay!
So let's enjoy this!
Yay! Whoo!
楽しもう！
Let's enjoy this!
Yay! Woohoo!
ギラギラ
[Title: Gira Gira]
あーもう本当になんて素晴らしき世界
Ah, yet another wonderful world
んで今日もまた己の醜悪さに惑う
Today, too, I am bewildered by my own ugliness
だのに人を好きって思う気持ちだけは
But the feelings of wanting to like someone...
Though I still have this feeling to love someone
一丁前にあるから悶えてるんでしょう
That’s why I suffer
Ugly 正直言って私の顔は
Ugly, honestly my face is
そう神様が左手で描いたみたい
like God’s painting in left hand
必然 この世にあるラブソングはどれひとつ
Inevitably, all the love songs that exist
絶対 私向けなんかじゃないでしょう
Are not meant for me
使い道のないくちづけ
Kisses I can't use
憐みを恣に
mercies as I want
スパンコールの瘡蓋で身を守る
Protect myself with scab of spangles
愛されないくらいなんだ
People don't love me, so what
ギラギラ輝いて私は夜を呑み
Gira Gira I shine bright and swallow the night
Rap Tap Tap Tap
今に見みてろこのluv
Just you wait and see my love
目に染みるは1mgの花火
1mg of fireworks that soars my eyes
Drag on Drag on
なんてファニー この世はビザール
How funny, the world is so bizarre
ギラ ギラギラ ギラ
Gira Gira Gira Gira
Unknown お釈迦様も存ぜぬうちに
Unknown, before Buddha even knew
もう健やかに狂っていたみたい
Seems it has already been crazy
それは世界の方かそれとも私の方ですか?
Is it the world or myself?
共生は端からムリでしょう
Co-existence has been impossible from the start
マガイモノこそかなしけれ
Imitations are sad
無我夢中疾る疾る
I ran and ran for my life
強い酸性雨が洗い流す前に
Before that strong acid rain washes it off
蛍光色の痣抱いて
I embrace my fluorescent bruise
メラメラ火を噴いて私は夜の狼
Mela Mela I blow fire, I’m a wolf of the night
Rap Tap Tap Tap
そこで見てろこの乱舞
Stay there and watch me dance
強くおなり あなたなりの武装メイクアップで
Be strong with the make-up of yours
Flap up Flap up
不意に不安に
Unexpectedly, anxiety strikes
孤独は燃料 卑屈な町を行いく
Loneliness is gasoline, I visit obsequious towns
目を閉じて
Close my eyes
もういいかい もういいかい
am I ready? am I ready?
もしも神様が左利きなら
If God is left handed
どんなに幸せか知れない
I can’t imagine how happy I’ll be
ギラギラ輝いて私は夜を呑み
Gira Gira I shine bright and swallow by night
Rap Tap Tap Tap
今に見みてろこのluv
Just you wait and see my love
目に染みるは1mgの花火
1mg of fireworks that soars my eyes
Drag on Drag on
なんてファニー この世はビザール
How funny, the world is so bizarre
ギラ ギラギラ ギラ
Gira Gira Gira Gira
ギラギラ Give Love 花は満ちて(ギラギラ)
Give Love, flowers bloom (Gira Gira)
ありのまんまじゃいられない
Nobody can just be the way they are
誰も彼も なんて素晴らしき世界だ!
Ah, what a wonderful world!
ギラついてこう
Let's shine on
This stream depicts events for dramatization and may differ from the official canon.
“This stream depicts events for dramatization and may differ from the official canon.”
Fall in Grace: Ouro Kronii Birthday Live 2026
[Title: Fall in Grace: Ouro Kronii Birthday Live 2026]
Fall in Grace | Ouro Kronii Birthday Live 2026
[Title: Fall in Grace | Ouro Kronii Birthday Live 2026]